Guide to the Rice University Assistant to the President papers: Carl MacDowell, 1963-2001 (bulk 1990-1998) UA 084
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Off Campus - General, 1982 - 2001
  - WAC, July 1998 (Collapse) (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - WAC, August 1998 (Collapse) (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - WAC, August 1998 (Collapse) (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - WAC, September 1998 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - WAC, October 1998 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - WAC, November 1998 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - WAC, December 1998 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - WAC/Gillis Announcements, 1994 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - WAC/Gillis Files, 1994 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - WAC/Meetings, 1994 - El Paso, TX (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - WAC/Meetings, 1995 - San Diego, CA (NCAA) (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - WAC/Meetings, 1995 - Park City, UT (Box 176, Folder 9)
  - WAC/Meetings, 1996 - Colorado Springs, CO (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - WAC/Meetings, 1997 - Monterey, CA (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - WAC/Meetings, 1998 - Tucson, AZ (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - WAC/Meetings, 1998 - Spanish Bay, CA (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - WAC/Press, 1994 (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - WAC/Schedules, 1994 (Box 177, Folder 6)
- Series IV: Chronological Correspondence Files, 1992 - 2000
  The material is this section is made up of photocopies of correspondence generated from the President's Office. (Rupp – January 1992 to June 1993; Gillis – July 1993 to 2000). Most of the correspondence was for the President's signature, but there is some correspondence by Carl MacDowell and some by the president's assistant. The material is filed by year and each year is divided into months. The March 1999 file was not included, but the March 2000 was. As of June 2004, there are no other 2000 files.
  - 1992
    - January (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - February (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - March (Folder 1) (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - March (Folder 2) (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - April (Folder 1) (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - April (Folder 2) (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - May (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - June (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - July (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - August (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - September (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - October (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - November (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - December (Folder 1) (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - December (Folder 2) (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - 1993
    - January (Folder 1) (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - January (Folder 2) (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - February (Folder 1) (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - February (Folder 2) (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - March (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - April (Folder 1) (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - April (Folder 2) (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - May (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - June (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - July (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - August (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - September (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - October (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - November (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - December (Folder 1) (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - December (Folder 2) (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - 1994
    - January (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - February (Folder 1) (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - February (Folder 2) (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - March (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - April (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - May (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - June (Folder 1) (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - June (Folder 2) (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - July (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - August (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - September (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - October (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - November (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - December (Folder 1) (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - December (Folder 2) (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - 1995
    - January (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - February (Folder 1) (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - February (Folder 2) (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - March (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - April (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - May (Folder 1) (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - May (Folder 2) (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - June (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - July (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - August (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - September (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - October (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - November (Folder 1) (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - November (Folder 2) (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - December (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - 1996
    - January (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - February (Folder 1) (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - February (Folder 2) (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - March (Folder 1) (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - March (Folder 2) (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - April (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - May (Folder 1) (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - May (Folder 2) (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - June (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - July (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - August (Folder 1) (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - August (Folder 2) (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - September (Folder 1) (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - September (Folder 2) (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - October (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - November (Folder 1) (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - November (Folder 2) (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - December (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - 1997
    - January (Folder 1) (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - January (Folder 2) (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - February (Folder 1) (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - February (Folder 2) (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - March (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - April (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - May (Folder 1) (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - May (Folder 2) (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - June (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - July (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - August (Folder 1) (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - August (Folder 2) (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - September (Folder 1) (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - September (Folder 2) (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - October (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - November (Folder 1) (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - November (Folder 2) (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - December (Folder 1) (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - December (Folder 2) (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - 1998
    - January (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - February (Folder 1) (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - February (Folder 2) (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - March (Folder 1) (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - March (Folder 2) (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - April (Folder 1) (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - April (Folder 2) (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - May (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - June (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - July (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - August (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - September (Folder 1) (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - September (Folder 2) (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - October (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - November (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - December (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - 1999
    - January (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - February (Folder 1) (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - February (Folder 2) (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - March – No March files included (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - April (Folder 1) (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - April (Folder 2) (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - May (Folder 1) (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - May (Folder 2) (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - June (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - July (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - August (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - September (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - October (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - November (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - December (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - 2000
    - March (Folder 1) (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - March (Folder 2) (Box 206, Folder 2)